<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> </title>
    <link>http://amritargupta.github.io/blog/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author></author>
    <rights>(C) 2015</rights>
    <updated>2015-05-02 10:04:56 &#43;0530 &#43;0530</updated>

    
      
        <item>
          <title>Unexpected Love</title>
          <link>http://amritargupta.github.io/blog/2015/05/02/unexpected-love</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 10:04:56 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>http://amritargupta.github.io/blog/2015/05/02/unexpected-love</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;While slowly sipping from hot cut of tea waiting to start my day thinking about how i woke up with the sunlight on my face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feeling the cold breeze around myself, i took few minutes to get out of bed. The sweet smell of the flowers is coming from the window just like everyday. Its now a part of my every morning, walking around in the garden, smelling the sweet flowers, enjoying every second of the stroll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly i was jolted back with my mother&amp;rsquo;s voice &amp;ldquo;Nisha, Are you listening .. Your phone is ringing &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ran to my room and picked the call and spoke &amp;ldquo;Hello&amp;rdquo; into the speaker.
From the other side someone replied &amp;ldquo;Hey Nisha, Do you remember me .. I am Kabir ..&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was stunned for some time, i was sure i was in some dream. The again from the other side of the phone came sound &amp;ldquo;Are you there .. &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I replied in a shivering voice replied &amp;ldquo;I am here .. &amp;ldquo;. Kabir asked &amp;ldquo;Do you remember me .. &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I remember .. &amp;rdquo; said I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said &amp;ldquo;i want to meet you .. &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kabir and I were really good friends in college. But after college he landed a job and we never met or talked again. I also went for my higher studies and got busy with my job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am still here .. Nisha please speak something .. &amp;rdquo; Kabir said from other side of the phone.
I was not sure what to say, I said &amp;ldquo;We will meet sometime .. &amp;ldquo;. But Kabir insisted on meeting today. He requested a lot to meet me today. In the end i gave up and said Ok we will meet and we decided to meet in evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In college time we were really good friends, and used to talk a lot. Our friends used to tease us saying there is something happening between you two, but Kabir never noticed these things. I used to always like him, but Kabir never talked about it and never showed any interest. Probably because of this i kept my feelings to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entire day i was thinking about &amp;ldquo;Why Kabir want to meet me. He has moved ahead in his life. I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether he is married or not. Will he come alone or with his wife.&amp;rdquo; These were the thoughts running through me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was unable to concentrate on any tasks in office, unable to complete any work and was entirely occupied with these thoughts. I left from office early today. When i reached home mom asked Nisha you came early today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said i am going out and would be coming late. I left from the house but got stuck in traffic jam. There were lot of questions running in my mind and as i was nearing the hotel i started getting more and more nervous. I reached quite late due to the heavy traffic jam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After parking the car, i walked towards the hotel and saw Kabir standing in front of the hotel waiting for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When i reached nearer he said &amp;ldquo;Hello Nisha .. How are you .. &amp;ldquo;.
I said &amp;ldquo;I am good .. &amp;ldquo;. He said &amp;ldquo;You have not changed, Your face is glowing the same it used to when you were in college ..&amp;rdquo;. I said &amp;ldquo;lets go inside ..&amp;rdquo;. He said &amp;ldquo;So sorry, I totally forgot. Looking at you.&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The manager met us in front of the hotel and let us inside the hotel. He took us inside and directed towards the grand hall. Kabir insisted that i should go inside first. I opened the door and was stunned. The whole area was filled with roses, walls were decorated with Red ballons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was totally stunned, I asked Kabir &amp;ldquo;Whats this .. &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He led me inside and said &amp;ldquo;Nisha, I love you .. I have always liked you .. and i wish to marry you .. &amp;ldquo;. I was totally shocked, stunned and looking at Kabir&amp;rsquo;s face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So many thoughts were going through my mind &amp;ldquo;Is this real&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;I must be sleeping&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;This is unbelivible&amp;rdquo;, but my deep feelings for him bought a smile on my face. I have always liked him and waited for this proposal but during our college time it never came. He bought a big rose bouquet for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said again &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Nisha will you please marry me&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. I took the bouquet and said yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lovely dinner and talked a lot, he told me later that today is Valentines&amp;rsquo; day when people tell there feelings to whom they like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had totally forgotten about this after Kabir&amp;rsquo;s phone came in morning. This happened to be most memorable day of my life and i want to remember it every time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    

  </channel>
</rss>
